needlive.com 2011-03-21

# NeedLive.com - The number one live adult webcam community

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

### **(1) What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views)

(b) on our online registration form, we ask you to provide us a username, password and e-mail address. Additionally, we collect address, credit card, and bank information only from those who wish to use our VIP member program. **However, NONE of the personally identifiable information can be accessed or used by the public to identify a specific individual**

(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including username, password, e-mail address)

(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters

(e) any other information that you choose to send to us

### **(2) Cookies**

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use cookies on the website to keep track of you whilst you navigate the website and to improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website and enable our website to recognise you when you visit. Cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available [here](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html).

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies, this will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites including this one.

### (3) Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a) administer the website;

(b) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;

(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;

(d) resolve technical issues relating to the website;

(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;

(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

(h) send you occasional newsletters and other marketing communications relating to our service which we think may be of interest to you by e-mail or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);

(j) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website (e.g. member's profile page), we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

We will **NOT** provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing or any other purposes!

All our website financial transactions are handled through our authorized payment service providers (CCBill, CommerceGate, Epoch, ClickandBuy and ePassport). We will share information with these providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.

### (4) Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to our employees, insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you: 

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);

### **(5) International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the EEA. 

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website (member's profile page) will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

### (6) Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password or credit card number.

### **(7) Your use of Other Users' Information**

You may not use other user’s information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. We reserve the right to terminate those user accounts who misuse other user’s information or who otherwise violate our Terms of Use. 

### **(8) Control of Your Password**

You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

###  (9) Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

### **(11) Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

### (10) Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to help[at]needlive.com

NeedLive.com Privacy Policy  
Updated: 2008-10-20
